# Tiya Gallegos Full Stack Developer Speech Language Pathologist (SLP)

Denver, CO 80247 | 714.294.8156 | tiyaagallegos@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tiya-gallegos | github.com/tiyagallegos | https://www.tiyagallegos.com

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

Front-End Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SASS, SCSS, ES6

JavaScript Ecosystem: Webpack, NPM, Gatsby, Netlify, Firebase, Heroku

Backend Development: Node, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Python, Django, Flask

JavaScript Frameworks/Libraries: React, Express, React Router, Dom, Bulma, Bootstrap, Materialize, Mongoose, Axios, jQuery

Version Control: Git, Github

Tools: AWS, Stripe, WebSocket, bCrypt, codepen, visual studio code, Atlas

#### PROJECTS:

#### Exchange: Django, Python, Bulma, Stripe, bcrypt

An E-commerce marketplace app implementing Stripe highlighting values of scalability, safety, and user-friendly UI. https://cyberpunk-exchange.herokuapp.com/

#### GYB: Full stack MERN spa

An app that aims to provide community-based support to help decrease the amount of violence experienced by the QTPOC community. Members of the QTPOC community and allies are able to accompany QTPOC to their destinations safely in small groups even if a vehicle is not available.

https://got-yo-back-p3.herokuapp.com/

#### YuMMY!: MEN stack application with google Oauth

An agile pediatric feeding data tracking app to provide therapists and parents with an easy to use platform to document patient progress and provide resources and education.

https://p2-yummy.herokuapp.com/

#### RiRi on Repeat: JavaScript, API, ¡Query

A web app implementing music API to render song information and a short audio clip based on search of song titles. aithub.com/tivagallegos/tivagallegos.github.jo

## **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

# Solace Home Healthcare (SLP & Clinical Mentor) Denver, CO

June 2018-Present

- Provided speech and language services through consultation, inclusion support, and individual instruction
- Administered individual evaluations, developed treatment plans, and carried out treatment plans in individual settings
- Clinical Mentor Facilitated meetings involving chart audits, clinician support, and collaborative multidisciplinary problem solving

## Let's Talk Therapy Clinical Manager (Management & SLP Supervisor) Duluth, GA

June 2016-May 2018

- Provided speech and language services through consultation, inclusion support, and individual instruction
- Administered individual evaluations, developed treatment plans, and carried out treatment plans in individual settings
- Management duties: scheduling, insurance correspondence, evaluation/plan of care coordinator, supervision of SLPA, and clinical fellow, consults, new hire orientation, hiring/applicant process/interviews
- Pediatric Feeding Clinic: developed policy and procedures for LTT feeding clinic, pediatric feeding mentor/supervisor
- In-service coordinator and presenter; Community outreach consultant and coordinator

# **Denver Public Schools (Full Time SLP and Supervisor)** Denver, CO 2016

July 2015-June

- Provided speech and language services through consultation, inclusion support, small group and individual instruction
- Administered individual evaluations, developed treatment plans, and carried out treatment plans in group/individual settings
- Attended and participated in IEP meetings; Case management; Experience with Medicaid documentation in school settings
- Managed and mentored SLPA

#### **EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES:**

Software Immersive Engineering, General Assembly M.S., Speech Language Pathology B.S., Speech, Language and Hearing Sciences Professional Women's Soccer 2012-2014